*
(TV clicks on)
RONALD REAGAN:
East and West
do not mistrust each other
because we're armed.
We're armed because
we mistrust each other.
Mr. Gorbachev,
tear down this wall.
(cheering and applause)
("Blue Monday '88"
by New Order plays)
(grunting and panting)
-(grunting)
-(tires squealing nearby)
*
(tires squealing)
(grunting)
* How does it feel
* To treat me like you do?
(yells, grunts)
* When you've laid your hands
upon me *
-(engine revving)
-* And told me who you are
(tires squealing)
-(yelling)
-* I thought I was mistaken
* I thought I heard
-* Your words
-(yelling in pain)
* Tell me, how do I feel?
(playing over car stereo):
* Tell me now, how do...
MAN (laughing):
James fucking Gascoigne.
How did you find me?
Maybe you're not as good
at this spy shit as you think.
It was Satchel, wasn't it?
Satchel gave me up.
(groans, pants)
I always thought,
if I got tagged,
it would be by the best.
But you're not the best,
are you, Bakhtin?
You're the biggest fucking cunt
in the KGB.
(chuckling)
Sticks and stones, Jimmy.
(gunshot echoing)
*
(ticking)
(grunting)
(splash)
(sighs)
(ice cubes clinking)
*
(gasping breaths)
("Cat People"
by David Bowie plays)
* See these eyes so green
(light clicks, buzzes)
* I can stare
* For a thousand years
* Colder than the moon
* It's been so long
* And I've been
putting out fire *
* With gasoline
* See these eyes so red
* Red like jungle
burning bright *
* Those who feel me near
(car horn honks)
* Pull the blinds
* And change their minds
* It's been so long
* Still this pulsing night
* A plague I call a heartbeat
* Just be still with me
* You wouldn't believe
* What I've been through
* You've been so long
* Well, it's been so long
* And I've been
putting out the fire *
* With gasoline
* Putting out the fire
with gasoline. *
(buzzing, ringing)
(lock clunks, buzzes)
That's a nasty black eye.
Where's C?
Given the scale
of recent world events,
C will not be joining us.
Yes, of course.
(tape recorder clicks, hums)
(lock clunks and buzzes,
door opens)
The voices on record
are the following:
myself, Senior Directorate
Officer Eric Gray;
our American guest,
Emmett Kurzfeld
of the U.S.
Central Intelligence Agency;
and returning
British Operational Officer
Lorraine Broughton.
Before we begin, sir,
may I formally request
that Mr. Kurzfeld be removed
-from the debriefing.
-Request denied.
What I have to tell you, sir,
is not for the CIA to hear.
Lorraine, you are the subject
of this debriefing,
-not its controller.
-I understand that.
KURZFELD:
I was there, in Berlin.
And I'm here with the full
executive authority of Langley.
If it'd make you
more comfortable,
I could stand behind the mirror
with everybody else.
But it's a little crowded
back there.
(quietly):
Cocksucker.
What did you say?
I didn't say anything.
I'm sorry. Did you say
something, Lorraine?
Did you hear me say something?
-I thought you said something.
-What did she say?
LORRAINE:
What?
(Kurzfeld sighs)
Well...
do you want
to play the tape back?
(sighing):
Well, then...
Shall we begin?
Berlin.
What happened?
Yeah.
(chuckles softly)
Berlin.
(inhales deeply)
(long exhale)
Fuck.
(thunder rumbling)
GRAY:
Ah. Lorraine.
Sorry to bring you in
on such short notice.
You know C.
-Yes. -We were just
going over your file.
I see your Russian
is excellent.
An expert in escape
and evasion.
Proficient
in intelligence collection
and hand-to-hand combat.
It's an impressive set
of skills.
Knowing the Reds as I do,
she'll need to use
every damn one of them.
I'll get straight to the point.
How well do you know
James Gascoigne?
Enough to say hello.
We worked together
-in Istanbul in '85.
-He's dead.
Gascoigne was killed last night
on a mission in Berlin.
GRAY:
The West German Police
fished his body out
of the Spree this morning.
And the coroner extracted
a 7.62 Tokarev round
from the base of his skull.
Soviets.
Yesterday, Gascoigne met
with a Stasi officer,
code-named Spyglass.
We promised Spyglass immunity
in exchange
for a document on microfilm,
code-named "the list."
Hidden in a Swiss watch,
no less.
The list contains every active
clandestine officer,
all their shady deals.
It's an atomic bomb
of information
that could extend the Cold War
for another 40 years.
And we believe the man that
killed Gascoigne now has it.
Our sources point
to Yuri Bakhtin,
a KGB hatchet man with more
than a dozen confirmed kills.
LORRAINE:
So you want me in Moscow?
No.
Bakhtin never got
on the flight.
So he's still in Berlin,
along with the list.
Everyone's hunting for it.
The Yanks, the Frogs.
Soviets, of course.
GRAY:
And our man, Percival.
Who's Percival?
David Percival.
He's our number one in Berlin.
(slide projector clicks)
He's your point of contact now.
* Fight the power!
* Fight the power...
Straight from the tit
of the Virgin Mary.
* We got to fight
the powers that be *
* As the rhythm's
designed to bounce *
* What counts
is that the rhyme's *
* Designed to fill your mind
* Now that you realize
the pride's arrived *
* We got to pump the stuff
to make us tough *
* From the heart,
it's a start, a work of art *
* To revolutionize, make a
change, nothing's strange... *
The Jordache wasn't easy.
It's for my wife's birthday.
That's really nice.
Now, where's that fucking list?
I gave the microfilm
to Gascoigne last night.
James didn't show up.
I did my part.
I gave him the list.
You have to get me
and my family across.
It's not safe
for us anymore here.
The Russians are onto me.
No list, no deal.
* In order to fight
the powers that be... *
-I risked everything.
-No list, no deal.
You listen to me, Spyglass.
Without that list, why
shouldn't I take you outside
and shoot you
in the fucking head?
You are going to kill
a Stasi officer?
One that's about to defect
to the West? Yeah.
Without an embassy
to look after him,