Do you believe in
the existence of evil?
Help me!
Oh.
No!
30 years ago, I found
the Book of the Dead.
Now, because I read
from the book...
Missar-drah--
... evil has found me.
You have no idea
what you're doing!
Of course I know
what I'm doing.
I wrote this book.
Ruby is in Elk Grove,
Michigan.
That's my hometown.
Ash?
Hiya Pop.
I got a problem.
The book--
it did something to me.
It changed me.
Night night.
That's our cue!
Evil, if you show your ugly mug
in this town ever again,
I will take you down
and I will wipe you out!
You know me
as Ash Williams,
the hero who saved
Elk Grove from evil.
For 30 long years, I've used
this saw on monsters and demons.
But those battles are won,
so now I use it to--
Slash prices!
At Ashy Slashy's Hardware
Store Emporium,
we got you covered!
You want paint?
We shake it till
we break it!
Ladies,
you'll love his nuts!
What's better than
a handful of my nuts?
Ahh!
A long screw.
Whoa!
We got wood.
We got rope.
We got rubber!
We got it all!
Die high prices
Goodbye high prices!
For that special someone,
we've got everything from
- "D" to "ildo."
- Mmm.
Because at Ashy Slashy's,
service is literally...
Not.
... our middle name!
Whoo!
Perfection!
And only 22 takes!
- Welcome back...
- Yeah.
It's looking good,
Jefe.
Marketing 101,
Pablo.
Know your audience.
Look at them
lining up out there.
You're a badass!
You know I've never seen
a town lose its shit
over a hardware
store before.
Well, it's time
to wake up and smell
the lightly scented
wax flowers, Pablo.
This isn't just a well-stocked
hardware store/sex-toy emporium.
No, this is a shrine
to a local hero.
Those adoring
fans are my peeps!
All right!
Hey, hey!
Hello, Elk Grove!
Are you ready for some
hardware?!
Come on in!
Fishing supplies,
aisle two.
We got guns, we got flags,
we got pornography.
That's a little further
in the back.
Men, can't please
your wives?
Better check out
aisle seven.
Yeah!
Same problem?
No need to push, jeez.
Aisle 3 I think.
Hey, no need to push.
Leave me alone.
And last up we have Amy,
who I'm told has made
a startling discovery.
I see here, Amy, that
you discovered this item--
In the mud.
Well, I know. I'm sorry...
What I fucking
tell you, huh?
How many times
I got to tell you?
Pretzels are for paying
customers only!
Okay?
Next time I'll use your
head as a fucking cue ball.
Who touched the T--
who touched the TV?
How many fuckin'--
Hey, hey, it's me.
You were right,
evil's coming back.
And here you've found a book
written in ancient Sumerian.
Curious.
Does "curious"
mean valuable?
This appears
to be some sort of...
descriptive passage.
Conda anu astratta
alaktu...
You know with most
of these clowns,
I got to play hardball,
but for you?
Hose clamps
are half-off.
These are the best
in the world.
You put them on,
they grip tight.
They don't slip, slide, stretch,
or tear like other things.
... estaro ces reche.
Sarr des kanda...
Kanda...
kanda?
What?
Apparently you've found
an ancient text,
known as the
Necronomicon-Ex Mortis.
The Book of the Dead.
Is that... good?
The book,
is said to hold spells
and incantations that,
if read out loud...
... could connect the demons
of the netherworld,
with our own--
Most important
thing about a hose,
is its width,
and its length.
Mostly the length.
Our scheduled broadcast
will resume
in a moment.
Hey!
I paid for
two more spots!
Okay, we got two
fish tacos.
Bam!
We got your
hard drive.
That's me. Thank you.
Enjoy.
Oh yeah.
Oh!
I don't know...
Excuse me.
Oh! Shit--
Who are you?
Well in Rome, they called me
mulier daemonium de igne.
Demon woman of fire.
And in Greece,
they called me
ágria ti mitéra
apó tin kólasi.
Fierce mother from hell.
But in these benighted times,
they just call me Ruby.
I'll take that.
No! No! Wait!
It's too important--
This is bullshit.
Whatever happened
to free speech?
Ah, this was my best
giant penis yet.
Yeah.
Thanks for talking me into this.
You missed a spot.
Dick.
Less.
Can we just finish
and get out?
I'm in enough
trouble already.
Wait till they see what
I drew on Perkins' car.
Is "man-gina" a word?
Oh, Rachel, please.
I just want to get through
the next four months.
Since when did you become
Miss Bourgeoisie?
Oh, it's simple.
I graduate,
I can leave here.
I leave here, I'm not here,
and that's a good thing.
All right, you still haven't
fallen for Elk Grove's
"small town charms?"
Excuse me?
The whole town's excited
because their ex-psycho killer
is opening
a hardware store.
Kill me now.
Could be worse.
How?
We could be like them.
Oh, yeah.
That'll never happen.
Good, because
if you did,
I would have
to slit my wrists.
Oh, look.
Cougie's back.
Yeah, well,
fuck off, Cougie!
Okay, we get it.
Costume, mascot,
very funny.
You can leave now!
Hey, asshole!
Go away--
Shit.
Okay, guy, now I'm mad.
Jesus, what is that?
Probably just some
varsity assholes
playing some
bullshit prank!
Ah!
Brandy, don't!
What is your problem,
fuckboy?
Help!
Help please!
And that's
the whole story.
Hey, feller.
Hey. How are you?
Ladies. Come on.
A litlle somethin',
somethin'.
There we go.
Nickel for a tickle, huh?
What do you say?
I don't believe this,
it's really him.
- Oh, hey. Hey, honey.
- Mom! Mom!
There's this guy at the school,
you've got to come
help us, please!
What?
Hey, Pablo.
Yeah.
Ah, I got to talk to you about
something else.
If this is about
a raise--
Actually, you don't pay me
at all right now, but--
Son of a bitch!
Hey, whoa!
Lady!
There's a line!
Wha-- ? You don't
even remember me?
Well, the old steel trap
never forgets a rack,
but faces are
a little fuzzy.
Give me a hint.
I said a hint.
I'm your fucking wife!
My what?
We need to talk.
Lady, I don't know what
kind of coo-coo juice
you've been drinkin',
but if you're fishing
for alimony--
One of your goddamn monsters
just attacked our daughter
at Kenward County High.
Daughter?! Ha!
You definitely
got the wrong guy!
Demons made you
chop off your hand.
"I'll swallow your soul."
Good sex is 30 seconds
followed by a cheeseburger?
Okay, maybe we have met.
But in case you didn't
get the memo,
me and my compadres,
we buried evil big time.
Elk Grove is officially
a demon-free zone.
Jefe.
Yeah.
I think she's telling
the truth.
Dude, I told you to get that
shit lasered off.
Nah, I didn't
do this!
It just happened outside.
I'm scared!
This thing is after
my little girl and--
All right all ready!
I'll check it out!
Just like old times,
eh, Pablo?
Except for the wife part,
and no Kelly.
Actually, it's not like
old times at all.
Just drive!
Hey, easy for you sister.
You come waltzing
into my life,
yapping about demons
and daughters,
and I don't know
boo about you.
Candace Barr.
Yeah, and?
Branson?
Branson.
Oh...
Oh.
Ah! My God!
Oh God! She's so good!
Oh.
Wait a minute,
Candace Barr.
Oh no, Candy Barr?
Well, this daughter
of ours,
I'll bet she thinks
I'm pretty special, huh?
Dream on.
I told her her old man
was some crack dealer
who got shanked in prison.
What?!
Well, it was easier
than admitting
I'd hooked up with
some psycho saw-boy!
Oh, okay, but I call
B.S. on the daughter.
I was using my lucky rubber
all through the odds,
and that sucker
went 50 and 0.
Oh, oh, oh.
Just drive!
Candalier boncelo....
Kanda.
Abomino.
God, that smell.
This monkey farm hasn't
changed in 30 years.
The caller you are trying
to reach is unavailable.
She's not answering.
You actually
went to school?
Yeah, these halls have
some sweet memories.
Met my first
Linda here.
Hey, give me
a second.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry, I don't
even know you,
but did I make a mistake
coming to Ash for help?
Ever since I hooked up
with El Jefe,
I've seen a lot of weird
shit go down.
He's always
had my back.
Well,
almost always.
There was this one time
I got cut in half.
What?
Yeah, but Ash went back
in time to save me.
It was so cool,
but also really weird,
because when we got back,
nothing seemed to have changed.
Maui Wowie.
It's my emergency stash.
I'll just put this bad boy away
for the appropriate time.
Brandy?
Shh, shh!
Whoever's out there,
fuck off!
Brandy?
Wow.
She's not yours,
dumb-ass!
Mom!
Honey!
Thank God!
Back off, Mama Bear!
Hey!
What are you doing?
The ink on my buddy
went nuclear,
that means evil is just
around the corner.
So your little peach could
be a bowel-sucking hell beast.
Mom, what's the chainsaw
geek doing here?
Oh, honey, uh, I don't know
how to tell you this,
but Ash, he's- he's ah-
he's your--
What she's trying
to say is, I'm your pop.
Father dearest.
The old sperm shooter.
What?
But you can call me Dad,
unless you're a Deadite,
then you can go fuck yourself.
So come on now, demon-spawn!
Show Daddy
what you got!
Okay, nobody move.
Alleged Daughter,
who else is in the room?
Um, you...
the guy with the hair...
... my mom, and--
Rachel?
Hey, Brandy's friend.
You want to keep it down?
Oh! Oh my God! Rachel?
What have you done?
What are you doing?!
Rachel!
Ah!
Blow.
No!
I love you, Brandy.
Oh!
Ugh!
Candy.
Mom!
Why you--
No!
Ashy Slashy, soon there'll
be nothing left of you...
... we'll destroy your seed
and your whore daughter too.
Sorry jailbait, my dance card
is a little full.
I'll have to squeeze you in.
Brandy!
Oh!
Suck on that,
Harpo.
Whew.
What... what?
I know.
It sucks.
I remember my first
taste of evil.
Oh, Cougie!
They got you too!
Ash!
Ah! Whoa!
Howdy fuckin' ho, boys.
Miss me?
Uh!
Well, looky
who's back,
and seriously rocking
the leather.
Who's the boy toy?
Kelly was right.
You are
the prophesied one.
This is Dalton.
He's with
the Knights of Sumeria.
The who with the huh?
It's an honor
to meet you.
I've been waiting for the chance
to battle this ancient evil
my entire life.
Yeah, he's
kind of a fan.
Who's the kid?
Oh, believe it or not,
that's my daughter.
Sandy.
Ah, Mandy.
Brandy.
And fuck you.
We're still getting
to know each other.
Okay, team,
it looks like evil's back,
and Elk Grove
is ground zero.
Kelly, Pablo.
Other guy,
you up for this?
One for all,
and all for one.
Uh, cute, but no.
Pablo?
Say it like
you mean it.
Ghost Beaters are back!
Fucking A,
right we are!
And evil...
oh, we're coming
for you.
I think now is the appropriate
time Pablo.
Sandy?